Oh! Nice!
I'm just about ready to take a stance and hold it in the stoned position.
I knew it, and the number of faces is getting bigger.
I can eat five.
Yum!
Great.
Let's do this so we can accumulate data on this and get an average here.
This is a good opportunity for both of you to use this to know your distance, so please do it.
Tomo-san, please start.
Wow! I'm so excited.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Please do.
Aah!
Well, well, well.
Well, well, well, well, well, well.
Yes, yes, yes, give me an average.
You're practicing now, aren't you?
Let's practice with that already.
Okay, thank you very much.
Nice shot.
Miracle, miracle, miracle.
Good.
Miracle happened.
Very nice shot
This is going to stop, isn't it?
Sixty yards.
I'm at 60 yards.
I heard if you hit a few balls, the average will come out.
I'll hit a few balls.
I tend to go this way, don't I?
Let's go left.
Why?
I think it's just a little too far.
It's too far away. It should be closer.
The further apart they are, the stronger the circle will be.
It makes the circle stronger. If they were closer, the circle would be straighter, but if they were farther apart, the circle would move in this way.
And since it is easy to get caught when the circle is short, I think it is probably getting caught a little bit more than it should.
I'll ask them to move a little closer. Oh, that's good. About the same level as now.
About this much. Yes, that's good.
More to the left.
Push in.
It's totally possible to hit a little to the right because you thought it would go left.
I see. Then, about this much.
Turn a little to the right, move to the right, and go straight.
Straight ahead, straight ahead.
Go straight from facing right.
Ooh!
That's an average of 64 yards.
Pitching average 64 yards.
That's in the morning.
And then there's height and stuff.
And then there's gym time.
And then there's the angle of landing.
Stopping on the green.
That's amazing.
If you keep doing that, you'll really get to know yourself.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
You've got a big smile on your face.
I'd like to know some tips on how to drive.
I'd like to know.
Position the ball left of center.
Left eye.
I'm basically at the heel of my left foot.
I've been told to hit it inside of here.
I hit it maybe a little more inside than that.
But I'm hitting it more to the left than to the middle.
It's better this way.
It's important to swing through with your face in the air.
Is it okay if my feet are a little open?
The driver should be the widest.
That's right.
You and Mire-chan both have your hands in the air when you set up.
It's better to angle them a little.
Like this.
You should hold your hands like this, like this, and then hold them like this, like this.
The club stick is here, so this side is heavier.
So if you don't support it like this
If you don't support it like this, when you swing it, it's going to fall down even more like this.
That's why it goes to the right.
The arm is fine.
But it's better to have a little angle here.
Angle here
With the club.
So it's closer to the same.
If you do it like this, it's too far away from the club, but if you drop it a little bit
But if you drop it a little bit, it's closer.
I think it looks good.
I see.
Rubbing the face is good.
That's good.
That's great.
That felt so good.
I'm so glad you did that.
It sure is.
It's flying.
I'm so happy.
Now for the mini-game.
I'd like to play a mini-game, a near-pin duel.
Yes, sir.
Just 60 seconds today.
That's what we were practicing earlier.
I was practicing earlier.
So you can go anywhere?
I can go anywhere.
Okay. Directions.
The green with the white flag on your right.
The white flag green on your right.
Let's hit it 60 yards.
Yes, sir.
Three balls each.
60 yards to the white flag.
Sixty yards.
I don't know if I can do that.
All I can do is just hit it.
I'll do it.
I'm going for it.
Sixty yards.
Wooo...
Oh, this feels good.
Here it comes.
If I get a pet in here, it's birdie.
It's in, it's in, it's in!
You pros are amazing. Thank you so much.
I can't do it like this.
I don't think I can do it.
We were about 60 at the cut.
That's right.
So, I tend to go this way.
Turn this way.
Right, right.
Let's do it.
Okay. Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, I went to a totally different place.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Can I just turn around and go straight?
Let's head straight.
I'm in, I'm in!
Stop, stop, stop!
Almost!
Oh, no! At least!
I'd like to be in there, in the green, but that was close.
Here we go.
Oh, that looks really good.
It's short.
Good, good, good.
Fly, fly, fly.
Wow!
It's so close!
What am I supposed to use for this?
This is it, right?
Is that it?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It rolls.
Not at all.
Uh-oh.
Wait, it's not responding.
I can't hit it. I can't hit it.
I'm not hitting it. I'm not hitting it.
Bunker.
Not even close.
Last one?
Oh, my God!
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
I danced, I danced, I danced.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
Nice.
Both of you.
Nice! I'm telling you!
That's great! I heard it's really great!
Yeah!
Thank you so much for today!
Thank you very much! Thank you so much! It was so much fun!
It was so much fun!
I learned a lot and had a lot of fun!
I followed what you told me to do.
I could feel that I was improving a lot when I was conscious of what I was doing.
We played a lot of games and it was a lot of fun!
It was a lot of fun!
Thank you so much!
I'm getting a little hungry.
Hungry? Oh, my God!
Yes, I am!
I love bread. I'm so happy!
Everything looked delicious, but I chose the ones I thought would be the best!
Thank you so much!
Can I pick one that looks like it's full of stuff?
It looks like it's full of them!
We're really into leeks and onions.
We got it first, though.
And it looks like Shonan.
Chigasaki, Shonan...
I wonder if it's from around here.
It's great!
Bon appétit!
Garlic.
This is it.
I was on tour in Asia until the other day.
I ate so much Chinese food that I gained 4 kilos.
My stomach swelled up.
I can eat five of these now.
That's great!
It's true.
It's really, really bad.
When did you two start doing something related to your current occupations?
I joined a dance school when I was in the first grade of junior high school because I liked dancing.
It was at that school that I formed a band.
So you went from dancing to being in a band, is that right?
It just happened one day.
It was like we started playing instruments at the same time.
When you were a freshman in high school?
So, yes, it's been 18 years now.
As a gajidoc band, we've never stopped playing, and we've never changed members.
We have the Guinness record for the longest active Guy's band.
That's amazing, isn't it? It's amazing.
We didn't think it would last that long.
We didn't think it would last or not.
We were so focused on what was right in front of us.
But when we realized that, we were grateful that it has turned out that way.
It's really amazing.
You have been working for a long time, haven't you, MIDE-chan?
That's right. The group itself is celebrating its 15th anniversary right now.
I joined the group about a year later, so now we are celebrating our 14th anniversary and entering our 15th year.
I was in the first year of junior high school. I was just in the beginning of the first year of junior high school.
Ebichu was also involved in activities together, like attending Nico Junior High School.
We were together several times at festivals and music shows.
For a while, we were really close to each other.
At that time, we were like babies.
I was surprised to see how much he had grown.
I never thought I would be able to work with you on a golf show.
It was definitely not a music show.
How old were you when you started playing golf?
My family owned a driving range.
Wow!
Dense water!
I've been playing golf since I was a little kid, but I didn't really start until I was 9 years old.
I started playing golf when I was 9 years old.
Nine?
I haven't...
You don't know? How old am I?
Wait a minute, 20...
20... what? I've been playing golf for 20...
More than 20 years?
Yes, over 20 years.
Wow!
I really wish my parents had a driving range...
You can practice all you want.
Yes!
But don't you ever get a little sick of it?
When I feel like I can practice all I want, I don't.
And then I finally rebel.
Nowadays, the customers who used to come to our practice are very supportive of us.
They've been watching us since we were little.
I'm grateful for that.
What do you mean by continuity?
I just realized that I've been doing this for more than 20 years.
I think it's very hard to keep going for such a long period of time, and I think it's amazing to keep going when it comes to other people, but when it comes to myself, it's like, "I don't remember that.
It's a long period of time, but when I look back on it, I can remember when I started doing it as if it was yesterday.
Recently, I've been seeing people who used to come to my concerts in elementary school with their kids.
I'm really glad that I've been doing this for so long.
I'm really glad that I've kept doing it, because you can't see it unless you keep doing it.
That's for sure.
I've also had fans get married and bring their children.
I've also had fans get married and bring their children to the show.
That's amazing.
It's like you're related to your fans.
You can't experience that kind of joy unless you keep going, and that's when I feel most glad that I've kept going.
I think music is a way to connect with people and to remember the moment in a vivid way.
I hear it and I'm like, "Wow!
It's something that stays with you, so it's really wonderful.
I think it's really wonderful.
Riko, on the other hand, is there something about golf that you find rewarding?
It's the same with the people who have been supporting me since I was a little girl, and I think it's really tough to go around the course with the 18, whether it's bad or good.
The weather is different, and anytime...
I'm always trying to do my best to make them happy with my support.
Thank you very much!
I'd like to thank you for all you've taught me today, but I have a present for you.
Scribble on it!
Thank you very much!
I'm so excited about your autograph!
Thank you so much!
Please listen to it!
LUMINUS means something like luminous itself...
Oh, jellyfish!
Yes, yes, yes!
That's why I chose jellyfish.
So that's what it means!
No matter what path we take
As long as we are luminous
No matter where we go, as long as we are luminous, we will have a bright future.
That's wonderful!
What a wonderful meaning!
I'm glad I have it too.
I was just talking about the apparel.
It's cute. It's perfect for Galfin.
Thank you very much. It's perfect to wear now.
The green coordinate. No, really.
No, really. The cap is cute.
Socks in black and white? Two colors.
This is a T-shirt with a logo on the chest.
It's a T-shirt with a logo on the chest.
It's a nice color.
I'm so happy.
It's so cute because it's wide.
I'm sure it's a good fit.
It looks great on you.
I'm sorry to do such a great gift, but...
I want it signed.
I want it the most.
I'm so happy
thank you so much
Thank you very much.
I can't use it.
Let's make it a force, let's make it a thing.
Thank you very much
Let's treasure it
Let's make it a good luck charm
I'm going to fly with it
It's going to fly straight.
I'll get my best score.
Thank you very much.
That was fun.
But I'm sure we'll be able to make it happen.
My sister is a real rain woman.
I'm sure you'll understand the magic of the shrine...
I'll make you one more drink... on a certain day.
I'm not going to do it on a certain day.
Thank you very much.